Guide to the Frederick R. Koch Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alphabetical Name List
  - Carlota, Empress, consort of Maximilian, Emperor of Mexico
    See also: Jilek, August, boxes 322-323, folders 1747-1760
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      All materials: FRKF 219
      - Annunziata, Maria, 1866 Sep 10 (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Maximilian, Emperor of Mexico, 1866 Aug-Sep (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Calling card of Empress Carlota, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Caruso, Enrico
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Niola, Emilia Tibaldi, 1920 Sep-Nov (Box 5, Folder 107)
        FRKF 758.1
        FRKF 758.3
      - Niola, Raffaele, 1920 Jan 1 (Box 5, Folder 108)
        FRKF 758.2
  - Chabrier, Emmanuel
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Chabrier, Marie Alice Dejean, [1886]-91 (Box 5, Folder 109)
        FRKF 719.1-2
        FRKF 915.5
      - Costallat, Georges, [1884 Sep 7] (Box 5, Folder 110)
        Recipient formerly identified as Emile de Najac
        FRKF 845a
      - Mendès, Catulle, [ca. 1885 May 15] (Box 5, Folder 111)
        FRKF 915
  - Chaminade, Cécile
    - MUSIC
      - Chanson slave
        - Score, 1879 Oct 25
          FRKF 972
  - Chapman, Frederic
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Contract for the Yellow Book, 1894 Apr 19 (Box 5, Folder 112)
        FRKF 1007
  - Charlotte of Belgium, Empress of Mexico
    See: Carlota, Empress, consort of Maximilian, Emperor of Mexico, box 5, folders 104-106
  - Charpentier, Gustave
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Dandelot, Arthur, [1900 Oct 6] (Box 5, Folder 113)
        FRKF 845b
      - [Hahn, Reynaldo?], 1894 Nov 20 (Box 5, Folder 114)
        FRKF 658.1
    - MUSIC
      - Le couronnement de la muse (solo voices, choruses, orchestra)
        - Fragment, n.d.
          FRKF 441
      - Unidentified
        - Fragments of drafts, n.d.
          Note of authentication by Claude Charpentier
          FRKF 441.5
  - Chopin, Frédéric
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Grzymala, Wojciech (to Auguste Léo), 1849 Nov 8 (Box 5, Folder 115)
        FRKF 525
      - Sand, George, [1843 Oct 29] (Box 5, Folder 116)
        Partly written by Maurice Dudevant
        FRKF 522
      - Unidentified, [1848?] (Box 5, Folder 117)
        FRKF 523
    - MUSIC
      - Cantabile, piano, B. 84, B-flat major
        - Music for piano, 1834 (Box 5, Folder 118)
          Accompanied by purchase invoice of a former owner
          FRKF 241
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Invitation to Chopin's funeral, printed, 1849 Oct 30 (Box 5, Folder 119)
        FRKF 526
      - Note, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 120)
        FRKF 524
  - Claudel, Paul
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Halévy, Daniel, 1925-32 (Box 5, Folder 121)
        FRKF 955
  - Cocteau, Jean
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Auric, Georges, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 122)
        FRKF 1048
        See also: Auric, Nora, box 5, folder 123
      - Auric, Nora, 1940-54 (Box 5, Folder 123)
        Includes postcard to Nora and Georges Auric, also signed by Jean Desbordes
        FRKF 1047c
      - Badenhausen, Rolf, 1952 Dec (Box 5, Folder 124)
        FRKF 1230
      - Berrichon, Paterne, 1922 Jan 29 (Box 5, Folder 125)
        FRKF 261
      - Bertin, Pierre
        See: Gaudier, René, box 5, folder 131
      - Delamain, Maurice, 1923-49 (Box 5, Folder 126)
        FRKF 649.5
        FRKF 1245.E05
        FRKF 1306
      - delle Donne, Marie, [mid 1920s] (Box 5, Folder 127)
        Includes letter to Marie and Robert delle Donne and Maurice Sachs
        FRKF 204
      - Dongrie, Jean, 1919 Dec 28 (Box 5, Folder 128)
        FRKF 1240
      - Dortu, Willy, 1923-63 (Box 5, Folder 129)
        FRKF 1306.1
      - Frank, Nino, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 130)
        FRKF 799
      - Gaudier, René, 1920-26 (Box 5, Folder 131)
        Includes postcard with note from Pierre Bertin
        FRKF 1245.A08
      - Guérin, Jean, 1958, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 132)
        FRKF 1231
      - Hoeck, Mary, 1949, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 133)
        FRKF 1233
        FRKF 1244
      - Hugnet, Georges, 1950-51 (Box 5, Folder 134)
        FRKF 798
        FRKF 1245.E08
      - Hugo, Jean; Hugo, Valentine, 1943 May (Box 5, Folder 135)
        FRKF 1245.E07
      - Hugo, Valentine (from Eugénie Cocteau), 1921 Nov 28 (Box 5, Folder 136)
        FRKF 1245.A01
      - Jallot, Marcel, 1951 Nov 14 (Box 5, Folder 137)
        FRKF 1245.E09
      - Kessel, Georges, [1920s]-30 (Box 5, Folder 138)
        FRKF 1050
        FRKF 1235
        FRKF 1239
      - Kihm, Jean Jacques, 1959 Jan 31 (Box 5, Folder 139)
        FRKF 1245.E14
      - Laloy, Louis, [1927 Dec 31] (Box 5, Folder 140)
        FRKF 1047b
      - Lander, Daniel, 1955 Aug 29 (Box 5, Folder 141)
        FRKF 1245.E11
      - Laure, Marie [Marie-Laure de Noailles], 1957 Jun 20 (Box 5, Folder 142)
        FRKF 1245.E12
      - Liebermann, Rolf, 1961 May-Oct (Box 5, Folder 143)
        FRKF 319
      - Martin du Gard, Maurice, [1922?], 1923 (Box 5, Folder 144)
        FRKF 1245.E03
        FRKF 1245.E04
      - Matarasso, Henri, 1957-62, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 145-147)
        FRKF 201
      - Mortier, Pierre, 1909-12, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 148)
        Includes invitation from Jacques Doucet
        FRKF 979
      - Niniteh, Mila, 1951 Jul 21 (Box 6, Folder 149)
        FRKF 1236
      - Peillard, Léonce, 1953-59, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 150)
        FRKF 1238a
      - Picabia, Germaine Everling, 1953, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 151)
        FRKF 203
      - Saint Jean, Robert de, [1927]-51, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 152)
        Accompanied by "Le poing final," by Cocteau, typescript, corrected
        FRKF 954
      - Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1958 May-Jul (Box 6, Folder 153)
        FRKF 951
      - Sert, Misia, [1913]-34, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 154-156)
        Includes letter in the hand of Jean Desbordes, with a postscript by him
        FRKF 198
      - Tessier, Valentine, 1939, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 157)
        FRKF 422
      - Turpin, Alice, [1920s]-36, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 158)
        Includes a dictated letter in the hand of Jean Desbordes
        Includes a postcard photograph of Cocteau
        FRKF 452
        FRKF 453
        FRKF 454
        FRKF 455
        FRKF 457
        FRKF 458
      - Vallette, Alfred, 1921 Jul 17 (Box 6, Folder 159)
        FRKF 1409
      - Willemetz, Albert, 1944-62 (Box 6, Folder 160)
        Accompanied by documents concerning Cocteau's La machine infernale, notes and reproduction of a drawing by Cocteau, and poem possibly by Cocteau
        FRKF 563
        FRKF 664
        FRKF 665
        FRKF 1245.E10
      - Unidentified, 19[12]-62, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 161)
        FRKF 355, FRKF 402, FRKF 456, FRKF 479a-b, FRKF 649.4, FRKF 952, FRKF 1049b, FRKF 1229, FRKF 1245.A02, FRKF 1245.A10, FRKF 1245.A11, FRKF 1245.E01, FRKF 1245.E02, FRKF 1245.E06, FRKF 1245.E13
        See also: Writings/Poems/"Tout le diable et son train", box 7, folder 184-185
    - WRITINGS
      - "A Bréval..."
        See: Unidentified fragments and notes, box 7, folder 194
      - "L'acteur", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 162)
        FRKF 950a
      - L'aigle à deux têtes (play): "Costumes et décors de L'aigle à deux têtes", [ca. 1946] (Box 6, Folder 163)
        FRKF 1241
      - L'alibi tragique (play): fragments, [before 1914]
        FRKF 200
      - Barbette, Vander
        See: Unidentified/Notes on Vander Barbette, box 7, folder 194
      - La belle et la bête (film): script for recorded presentation about the film, 1947 Feb 17 (Box 6, Folder 164)
        FRKF 953b
      - La belle et la bête (film): voice-over introduction, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 165)
        FRKF 1242
      - "Berthe Bovy, Marianne Oswald, mes interprètes", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 166)
        FRKF 1245.B07
      - Le boeuf sur le toit (cabaret): memoir of the opening, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 167)
        Accompanied by two photographs of the Fratellini brothers in costume
        FRKF 641
      - "Boutiques: conte": typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 168)
        FRKF 202
      - Bric-à-brac (play): drafts, with drawings, n.d.
        FRKF 411
      - "Le coq et l'arlequin" (response to criticism of André Gide), [1918?] (Box 6, Folder 169)
        FRKF 1234
      - "Le critique et le théâtre", [1946] (Box 6, Folder 170)
        FRKF 661
      - "L'église de Chauvigny", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 171)
        FRKF 660
      - "En ce qui concerne les honneurs..." (manifesto), n.d.
        FRKF 578
      - "En faveur de 16 millimètres", 1948 Jan (Box 6, Folder 172)
        FRKF 735
      - "Hommage à Molière" (speech), [1946] (Box 6, Folder 173)
        FRKF 239
      - "Il y a quelque chose d'atroce dans cette habitude humaine..." (essay on the death of Anna de Noailles), 1933 May 1 (Box 6, Folder 174)
        FRKF 407
      - "Je demande au père Noël...," with self-portrait, 1955
        Dated "Noël, 1955"
        FRKF 1245.C05
      - "Le jeune fille de Ver Meer", n.d. (Box 6, Folder 175)
        FRKF 1245.B08
      - "Les jeunes ont coutume de s'appuyer sur la présentation d'un aîné..." (preface to book by Georges Noel) (Box 7, Folder 176)
        FRKF 406
      - "Jusqu'à nouvel ordre..." (preface to book by [Fernand?] Imhauser), with illustration, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 177)
        FRKF 974
      - "Lettre à Jacques Maritain" (essay): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 178)
        FRKF 846
      - La machine infernale (play)
        See: Correspondence/Willemetz, Albert, box 6, folder 160
      - "Mais qui peut comprendre? Personne" (article on the death of Anna de Noailles), 1933 May 1 (Box 7, Folder 179)
        FRKF 405
      - Les mariés de la Tour Eiffel (ballet): libretto, with drawings of the set, n.d.
        FRKF 1413
      - "Les noces de sable": two drafts, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 180)
        FRKF 421
      - Orphée (play): introduction, [1926?]
        FRKF 659
      - Parade (ballet): text for concert program, n.d.
        Accompanied by printed program, 1917 Jun 6
        FRKF 916
      - Les parents terribles (play): introduction, [1938?] (Box 7, Folder 181)
        FRKF 953a
      - Petition requesting pardon for Jean Genet, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 182)
        Accompanied by copies, typescript mimeograph, with typed signatures of Cocteau and John-Paul Sartre.
        Individual copies signed by:
        Achard, Marcel; Anouilh, Jean; Arland, Marcel; Aurenche, Jean; Auric, Georges; Autan-Lara, Claude; Aymé, Marcel; Bernardet, J.-C.; Dullin, Charles; Gallimard, Gaston; [Herbart?], Pierre; Lacombe, Georges; Marcel, Gabriel; Maulnier, Thierry; Poulenc, Francis; Rousset, David; Salacrou, Armand
        Accompanied by letters of support by:
        Autan-Lara, Claude; Breton, André; Péret, Benjamin; Prévert, Jacques
        FRKF 1248c
      - "Un phénomène extraordinaire de notre époque...", n.d. (Box 7, Folder 183)
        FRKF 1237
      - Poems, 1906-56, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 184-185)
        Includes:
        "A mon livre" FRKF 950c
        "Ascenceur" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Avis" FRKF 404
        "Cadran solaire" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Le Cap de Bonne Espérance" FRKF 1245.B02
        "Un cauchemar" FRKF 1245.D04
        "C'est en or précieux..." FRKF 1245.D03
        "Chanson pour elle" FRKF 1245.D01
        "Compliment" FRKF 401
        "Conte" FRKF 649.3
        "Danseuse" FRKF 1047a
        "Désir": fragment FRKF 1245.D01
        "Deux faibles" FRKF 1245.B01
        "École de guerre" FRKF 1047a
        "Gaufres manèges tirs cirques feux d'artifice...": typescript, corrected FRKF 403
        "Gravité du coeur" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Hommage à Bernard Buffet: gisant debout" FRKF 450
        "Mémoire" FRKF 354
        "Mouchoir" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Photographie" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Physique amusante" FRKF 1245.D05
        Poem on a Stradivarius violin ("Harmoniques n'importe où...") FRKF 1049a
        "Portrait: souvenir de Jules César," FRKF 1245.B01
        "Les primitifs" FRKF 1245.B01
        "Romance" FRKF 649.1
        "Le secret du bleu" FRKF 1245.D05
        "Soir sympathique et inutile," with unidentified poem on verso FRKF 1245.D02
        "Températures": fragment FRKF 649.2
        "Tout le diable et son train (ébauche d'un poème)," with autograph letter, signed, to unidentified on verso FRKF 1245.D07
        "Le vase" FRKF 1245.D01
        "Vous caressez votre menton..." FRKF 1047a
        See also: Correspondence/Willemetz, Albert, box 6, folder 160
      - "Le poing final"
        See: Correspondence/Saint Jean, Robert de, box 6, folder 152
      - "Préface" to Henri Matarasso, Vie d'Arthur Rimbaud, [1959] (Box 7, Folder 186)
        FRKF 199
      - "Premier verre de purge est bu..." (response to questionnaire): draft and proof, [ca. 1928?] (Box 7, Folder 187)
        FRKF 950b
        FRKF 950d
      - "Reconnaiss[ance] au public d'Allemagne" (preface to an unidentified work), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 188)
        FRKF 1245.B09
      - "Rien ne se croyait moins vu..." (preface to a work by Germaine Everling Picabia), 1953 (Box 7, Folder 189)
      - Roméo et Juliette (adaptation of Shakespeare's play): public talk, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 190)
        FRKF 1245.B06
      - "Les ruines de l'exposition", n.d. (Box 7, Folder 191)
        FRKF 1245.B05
      - Le sang d'un poète (film): preface to the scenario, [1946] (Box 7, Folder 192)
        FRKF 1243
      - "Secrets de beauté" (aphorisms), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 193)
        FRKF 1245.B10
      - "Soignez la gloire de votre firme..." (preface and captions for a publication by Draeger), [ca. 1929]
        FRKF 1232
      - "Texte de le table tournante chez Jean Hugo..."
      - "Le théâtre est mort, vive le théâtre", n.d.
        FRKF 1086
      - Unidentified fragments and notes, [before 1914]-[30?], n.d. (Box 7, Folder 194)
        "A Bréval..." (list of names), with other notes and drawings FRKF 1245.C02
        "Les cauchemars," with drawings FRKF 1245.C01
        Fragment of a dialogue or interview FRKF 978
        Notes from a séance FRKF 1245.A07
        Notes on Vander Barbette FRKF 1311
        "Texte de le table tournante chez Jean Hugo..." FRKF 1245.D06
    - DRAWINGS
      See also: Writings/ Bric-à-brac (play), box 93, folder 1435
      See also: Writings/"Je demande au père Noël...", box 319, folder 1694
      See also: Writings/"Jusqu'à nouvel ordre...", box 7, folder 177
      See also: Writings/ Les mariés de la Tour Eiffel (ballet), box 64, folder 1406
      See also: Writings/Unidentified fragments and notes, box 7, folder 194
      - Erik Satie, in pencil, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 195)
        FRKF 1419
      - Jean Cocteau, self-portrait, in charcoal, [1950s-60s?] (Box 7, Folder 196)
        FRKF 1245.C06
      - Jean Genet, in pencil, 1947
        FRKF 1248e
      - "Profile jaune," in pastel, signed, 1958
      - Raymond Radiguet, in pencil, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 197)
        FRKF 1245.A05
      - Raymond Radiguet and Georges Auric, in pen-and-ink (Box 7, Folder 198)
        FRKF 1245.A06
      - Other drawings, in pencil and pen-and-ink, [1923]-[after 1940], n.d. (Box 7, Folder 199)
        FRKF 1245.A04
        FRKF 1245.C03
        FRKF 1245.C04
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Photographs of Cocteau, [1920s] (Box 7, Folder 200)
        FRKF 1306.2
        See also: Correspondence/Turpin, box 6, folder 158
  - Cortot, Alfred
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Bernac, Pierre, 1957-60 (Box 7, Folder 201)
        FRKF 697
  - Coward, Noel
    - WRITINGS
      - Diaries
        All materials: FRKF 410e
        - Diaries, holograph, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 202-203)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1942-44 (Box 8, Folder 204-209)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1945-48 (Box 9, Folder 210-218)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1949-52 Sep (Box 10, Folder 219-225)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1952 Sep-57 Jun (Box 11, Folder 226-232)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1957 Jun-62 (Box 12, Folder 233-238)
        - Diaries, holograph, 1963-70 (Box 13, Folder 239-242)
        - Diaries, 1940-47, typed transcripts, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 243-251)
        - Diaries, 1948-56 Aug, typed transcripts, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 252-258)
        - Diaries, 1956 Sep-70, typed transcripts, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 259-264)
      - Other writings
        - After the Ball (operetta): fragments of lyrics, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 265-267)
          FRKF 410a
        - After the Ball (operetta): ozalids of excerpts from vocal score in copyist's manuscript, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 268)
        - Conversation Piece (play): drafts, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 269-270)
          FRKF 410b
        - Past Conditional (autobiography): notes
          FRKF 410c
        - Present Indicative (autobiography): incomplete draft of parts 1-9 (Box 18, Folder 271-279)
          FRKF 410d
        - Present Indicative (autobiography): incomplete draft of part 9 and unidentified (Box 18, Folder 280-281)
  - Cox, Palmer
    - DRAWINGS
      All materials: FRKF 60
      - Brownie Calendar, 1893: January-March, [ca. 1893]
      - Brownie Calendar, 1893: April-June, [ca. 1893]
      - Brownie Calendar, 1893: July-September, [ca. 1893]
      - Brownie Calendar, 1893: October- December, [ca. 1893]
  - Croisset, Francis de
    See: Robin, Louis, boxes 53-54, folders 1135-1155
  - D'Annunzio, Gabriele
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 282)
        FRKF 658.2
  - Daudet, Alphonse
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 283)
        FRKF 658.3
    - WRITINGS
      - L'Arlésienne (play): drafts and set sketches in three notebooks, [ca. 1871-72]
        FRKF 1297
  - Debussy, Claude
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Baron, Émile, 1887 Jan 5 (Box 19, Folder 284)
        FRKF 558a
      - Bréville, Pierre de, [1894 Feb 16?] (Box 19, Folder 285)
        FRKF 286
      - Debussy, Lilly
        See: Texier, Rosalie, box 19, folder 298-303
      - Diaghilev, Serge, 1917 May 20-26 (Box 19, Folder 286)
        Stamp: Serge Lifar
        FRKF 302
        FRKF 303
      - Dukas, Paul, [1896], 1901 (Box 19, Folder 287)
        FRKF 535a
        FRKF 558b
      - Émie, Louis, 1916 Dec 25 (Box 19, Folder 288)
        FRKF 470
      - Evans, Edwin, 1908-09 (Box 19, Folder 289)
        FRKF 1019
        FRKF 1076
      - Fromont, Eugène, 1901, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 290)
        FRKF 847
        FRKF 848
      - Fromont, Eugène, Madame, 1905 Apr 21 (Box 19, Folder 291)
        FRKF 849
      - Hartmann, Georges, 1899 Jan 15 (Box 19, Folder 292)
        FRKF 16
      - Kufferath, M. (Maurice), 1906 Aug 19 (Box 19, Folder 293)
        FRKF 285
      - Laloy, Louis, 1907 Mar 8 (Box 19, Folder 294)
        FRKF 161
      - Louÿs, Pierre, [1894-1901] (Box 19, Folder 295)
        FRKF 245
        FRKF 423
        FRKF 839
      - Mourey, Gabriel, 1913 Nov 17 (Box 19, Folder 296)
        FRKF 152
      - Poniatowski, André, 1893 Feb (Box 19, Folder 297)
        FRKF 160
      - Texier, Rosalie, 1899-1905 (Box 19, Folder 298-303)
        FRKF 197
      - Vuillermoz, Emile, 1913 Jun 24 (Box 19, Folder 304)
        FRKF 500
      - Unidentified, 1903 Dec 30 (Box 19, Folder 305)
        FRKF 5
    - MUSIC
      - Ariettes oubliées (songs)
        - Chevaux de bois: score, 1885 Jan 10
          FRKF 1138
        - L'ombre des arbres: score, 1885 Jan 6
          FRKF 713
      - Fêtes galantes, 2. recueil (songs)
        - Colloque sentimental, early version: score, n.d.
          FRKF 1139
      - La fille aux cheveux de lin (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          Includes unidentified sketches
          FRKF 1029
      - Hymnis (soprano, tenor, and piano)
        - Excerpt title "Ode bacchique": score and sketches
          FRKF 120
      - Intermezzo, violoncello, orchestra, C minor
        - Arrangement for piano, 4 hands: score, 1882 Jun 21
          FRKF 809
      - Jeux (ballet)
        - Short score, mostly in copyist's manuscript and revised in holograph, [1912]
          Annotations by Serge Diaghilev and Waslaw Nijinsky
          FRKF 301
      - Madrid, princesse des Espagnes (song)
        - Incomplete score, [1880]
          FRKF 14
      - Marche écossaise sur un thème populaire (piano, 4 hands)
        - Sketches, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 306)
          FRKF 287
      - Ode bacchique
        See: Hymnis (soprano, tenor, and piano), box 250, folder 1592
      - Pelléas et Mélisande (opera)
        Short score
        FRKF 15.1-2
      - Poèmes de Baudelaire (songs)
        - Le balcon: score, 1888 Jan
          FRKF 1354
      - Unidentified
        See: La fille aux cheveux de lin (song), box 319, folder 1704
        See: Madrid, princesse des Espagnes (song), box 320, folder 1706
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Pelléas et Mélisande, printed program, 1906 Nov 27 (Box 19, Folder 307)
        FRKF 535g
  - Delibes, Léo
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Unidentified, [1883] (Box 19, Folder 308)
        Probably to Georges Hartmann
        FRKF 810
  - Desbordes, Jean
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Turpin, Alice, 1928-[29?], n.d. (Box 19, Folder 309)
  - Donnay, Maurice
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Hahn, Reynaldo, 1926 Feb 27 (Box 19, Folder 310)
        FRKF 658.4
  - Douglas, Alfred Bruce, Lord
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Delarue-Mardrus, Lucie, 1930 Feb 13 (Box 19, Folder 311)
        FRKF 163
      - Shore, Mrs., 1942 Aug-Oct (Box 19, Folder 312)
        Formerly Mrs. Robinson
        FRKF 272
    - WRITINGS
      - "Stones for Bread" (sonnet), n.d. (Box 19, Folder 313)
        FRKF 349
  - Dukas, Paul
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Jean-Aubry, G. (Georges), 1919 Jul [27]-30 (Box 19, Folder 314)
        FRKF 766.1-2
      - Samazeuilh, Gustave, 1932 Aug 27 (Box 19, Folder 315)
        FRKF 164
    - MUSIC
      - Ariane et Barbe-bleue (opera)
        - Fragment in short score, n.d.
          FRKF 8
      - La fleur (chorus and orchestra)
        - Score, 1887 Apr 12
          FRKF 165
      - Polyeucte (overture)
        - Draft in short score, 1891 Sep 16
          Includes unidentified stage work, score, fragment
          FRKF 1392
      - Vélléda (cantata)
        - Short score, 1880-81
          FRKF 1348
      - Unidentified
        See: Polyeucte (overture), box 320, folder 1710
    - WRITINGS
      - "Ariane et Barbe-Bleue: moralité à la façon des contes de Perrault" (essay), [1910] (Box 19, Folder 316)
        FRKF 9
  - Dumas, Alexandre, 1824-1895
    - OTHER PAPERS
      - Album relating to La dame aux camélias, 1843-84, n.d.
        Includes materials relating to:
        Bernhardt, Sarah
        Dumas, Alexandre
        Duplessis, Marie
        [Eugénie, Empress, consort of Napoleon III, Emperor of the French?]
        Gramont, Antoine Alfred Agénor, duc de
        Le Vavasseur, Gustave
        FRKF 675
      - Papers removed from album, 1846 Jan 25
  - Duparc, Henri
    - MUSIC
      - Extase (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1393
      - L'invitation au voyage (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1394
      - Lamento (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1395
      - Le manoir de Rosemonde (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1396
      - Phidylé (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1397
      - Sérénade florentine (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1398
      - Testament (song)
        - Score, n.d.
          FRKF 1399
      - La vague et la cloche (song, voice and orchestra)
        - Arrangement for voice and piano by Vincent D'Indy: score
          FRKF 1400
  - Dvorák, Antonín
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Littleton, Alfred, [1884 Oct] (Box 19, Folder 317)
        Includes music quotation from The wedding gown
        FRKF 557
    - MUSIC
      - O sanctissima (solo voices and organ)
        - Version for soprano and alto: score without organ part, 1890 May 28
          FRKF 1030
      - Symphony, no. 8, op. 88, G major
        - Adagio, arrangement for piano, 4 hands: score, 1890 Oct 27
          FRKF 574
  - Edward VII, King of Great Britain
    - CORRESPONDENCE
      - Leighton, Frederick, 1895, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 318)
        Includes letter written by a secretary
        FRKF 1012
  - Egan, Pierce, 1772-1849
    - CORRESPONDENCE